Guide to the Consumer Reports. Audiovisual materials, 1940-2011 and undated RL.11802
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Consumer Reports. Audiovisual materials
1940-2011 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Consumer Reports (Firm)
RL.11802
90.00 Linear Feet
Consumer Reports is a product testing and consumer advocacy nonprofit organization based in Yonkers, N.Y., founded in 1936. The audiovisual materials collection consists of non-print materials in a variety of formats: audio cassettes and tape reels; film; optical disks; phonograph disks; videocassettes and video reels. Materials document a range of activities at Consumer Reports, including: Consumer Reports' radio and television productions; footage of product testing; appearances of Consumer Reports personnel on news programs; mentions of Consumer Reports in the media; press releases and other publicity; recordings of staff and Board meetings and staff speeches; and taped testimonies. The collection also contains some microfilmed documents and digitized elements of Consumer Reports' publications. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Arrangement
Organized into the following series: Advocacy and Consumer Education; Consumer Reports Publications; Consumer Reports Television; Iron Mountain Indexed Materials; Product Testing and Reviews; Public Relations and Publicity; Radio; Unidentified and Other Audiovisual Materials.
Biographical / Historical
Consumer Reports is a product testing and consumer advocacy nonprofit organization based in Yonkers, N.Y., founded in 1936.
Access Restrictions
Access restricted. Collection contains fragile audiovisual/photographic formats that may need to be reformatted before use. Contact Research Services for access.
Provenance
The Consumer Reports. Audiovisual materials were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2019.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
Consumer Reports Archives records
Consumer Reports. Board of Directors records
Consumer Reports. Colston E. Warne papers
Collection Overview
The audiovisual materials collection consists of non-print materials in a variety of formats: audio cassettes and tape reels; film; optical disks; videocassettes and video reels. Materials document a range of activities at Consumer Reports, including: Consumer Reports' radio and television productions; footage of product testing; appearances of Consumer Reports personnel on news programs; mentions of Consumer Reports in the media; press releases and other publicity; recordings of staff and Board meetings and staff speeches; and taped testimonies. The collection also contains some microfilmed documents and digitized elements of Consumer Reports' publications.
Consumer advocacy; Consumer education; consumer protection; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
- Advocacy and Consumer Education, 1940-2011; undated; 1
  - Automotive and Transportation, 1973-2006; undated; 1
    - 72 Kicking Tires is not Enough/ How to Buy a Used Car, Undated (Box 14, Film-reel RL11802-F16-070)
    - Airfares, 1974 May 31 (Box 76, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-084)
    - Auto Coverage 2000 w/Millionaire, 2000 May (Box 106a, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1072)
    - Auto Coverage 2000 w/Millionaire, 2000 May (Box 106a, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1073)
    - Auto Dealer tricks; Mariarce /WNJU / Telemundo Local, 2003 Apr.; Mar. 16 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1183)
    - Auto Defects, 1976 Feb. 18 (Box 70, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-149)
    - Auto FX Blood Lab, 1975 Aug. 14 (Box 70, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-150)
    - Auto Safety, 2002 May 28 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0679)
    - Automobile Financing Program #3 Reel 1, 1973 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-122)
    - Automobile Financing Program #3 Reel 2, 1973 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-121)
    - Automobile Insurance, is it a racket?, 1973 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-117)
    - Automobile Insurance, is it a racket?, 1973 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-118)
    - Auto-Safety, Undated (Box 72, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-007)
    - Avoidance Maneuvers - Tape A, Undated (Box 85, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0373)
    - Avoidance Maneuvers Tape A Confidential, Undated (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0171)
    - Behind the Wheel, 2004 Apr. 09 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0823)
    - Best Hotel Deals David Heims, 2004 June 24 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0777)
    - Black Gold, Undated (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-046)
    - Blind Spots, 2004 Sept. 08 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0852)
    - Buying an Auto Program #2 Reel 1, 1973 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-120)
    - Buying an Auto Program #2 Reel 2, 1973 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-119)
    - Car Leasing, 1998 Jan. 02 (Box 69, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0192)
    - Car Safety Tips, Jennifer Stockburger, 2003 Oct. 24 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0701)
    - Car Talk Plaza, Undated (Box 120, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-224)
    - Cars, 1986 (Box 83, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0446)
    - Cars, 1986 (Box 83, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0459)
    - Child Car Seats, 2005 May 11 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0863)
    - Consumer Union ETM IV Your First Car, 1980 Mar. 17 (Box 76, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-080)
    - Crashes That Need Not Kill, 1976 (Box 7, Film-reel RL11802-F16-008)
    - D. Champion & S. Greenberg Segment on Danger in Your Driveway, 2002 Nov. 21 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1225)
    - Dangers of Vehicle Blind Spots to Toddlers, 2005 May 20 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1146)
    - Dateline: Danger on the Road, 2000 Sept. 13 (Box 106, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1005)
    - David Champion Segment on Tire Pressure, 2002 Nov. 01 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1218)
    - David Champion The Danger of Blind Sports Behind Vehicles, 2003 Feb. 13; 2003 Apr. 28 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1209)
    - David Champion Today's Family Segment on SUV Safety, 2003 July 30 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1207)
    - Dealer Service; Used Cars Pt II, 1976 Feb. 26; 1976 Mar. 03 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-127)
    - Death on the Highway, Undated (Box 69, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0219)
    - Death on the Highway Head Pt 2, Undated (Box 3, Film-reel RL11802-F16-048)
    - Dialogo Con Glenis TopicoL Autos Usados, 2002 Apr. 10 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1214)
    - Driveway Dangers, 2002 Nov. 21; Dec. 04 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0735)
    - Firestone Tire Hearing, 2000 Sept. 06 (Box 106b, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1075)
    - Firestone Tire Hearing, 2000 Sept. 06 (Box 106b, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1076)
    - For Some Child Car Seats Slim Safety Margins, 2005 May (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0833)
    - Ford SUV Design Changes, 2000 Aug. 04 (Box 106b, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1077)
    - Gas Gadgets Part II, 1974 Aug. 30 (Box 76, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-086)
    - Gas Prices, David Champion, Consumer Reports, 2005 Sept. 08 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0786)
    - Government Rollover Ratings Proposal, 2000 Oct. 19 (Box 106, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1013)
    - How to Buy a car, 2003 Nov. 08 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1240)
    - I Got to Have Wheels, Undated (Box 76, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-092)
    - Jeff Blyskal - Car Insurance, 2002 Sept. 18 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1167)
    - Kicking Tires is not Enough/ How to Buy a Used Car #36, Undated (Box 14, Film-reel RL11802-F16-066)
    - Kicking tires isn't Enough, Undated (Box 33, Film-reel RL11802-F16-130)
    - Kicking Tires Theme #298, Undated (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-105)
    - KRON-TV Interview w/David Pittle Child Car Seats, 2002 Feb. 13 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0680)
    - Mr. Watson -- Interview (DOT) Auto Recall, Washington DC #190, 1975 July 10 (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-123)
    - NHTSA's New Rollover Ratings, 2001 Jan. 09 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1002)
    - Pantera, 1996 Apr. 27 (Box 85, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-213)
    - Purchase of a Second Hand Auto, Undated (Box 4, Film-reel RL11802-F16-037)
    - Rik Paul on Drivers Frustration over the Fuel Efficiency of Hybrid Vehicles an dhow the CR Fuel Efficiency Test Differs from the EPA's, ???? June 14 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1137)
    - Road Debris, Undated (Box 99, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0928)
    - Rob Gentile Hidden Cost of Dealer Extras, 2002 June 25 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1230)
    - Rob Gentile Segment on Car Buying Tips & 0% Financing, 2003 Feb. 20 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1170)
    - Segment on Teen Driving, Featuring Douglas Love Eyewitness News Sunday Morning, 2004 Nov. 28 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1095)
    - Segment on Tires; Segment on Autos, 2002 Nov. 02 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1213)
    - Stability Control, Undated (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0772)
    - Steering Clear of Lemons, Undated (Box 17, Film-reel RL11802-F16-076)
    - Steering Clear of Lemons, Undated (Box 34, Film-reel RL11802-F16-136)
    - SUV Debate, 2003 May 05 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0707)
    - SUV Rollovers, David Champion Consumer Reports, 2003 Oct. 07 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1180)
    - The SUV Safety Tutorial How Do You Ride?, 2006 (Box 1, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-009)
    - Tips on How to Buy a Used Car, 1999 Mar. 24 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0641)
    - Used Car Buying, 2003 Feb. 22 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1169)
    - Used Cars, Undated (Box 40, Film-reel RL11802-F16-144)
  - Consumer Protection, 1940-2011; undated; 2
    - 30-Second Seduction, 1985 (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0154)
    - 30-Second Seduction, 1985 (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0155)
    - 5-Min Video of Patient Safety Activists, 2007 June (Box 58, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-027)
    - A History of Consumer Protest, 1985 Mar. 13 (Box 88, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-199)
    - A Place to Hang Your Hat, Undated (Box 76, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-094)
    - Ads-With Filmstrips, Undated (Box 76, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-089)
    - America At Risk, 1985 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-324)
    - America At Risk, 1985 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-325)
    - America At Risk, 1985 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-326)
    - America At Risk, 1985 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-327)
    - America At Risk, 1985 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-330)
    - America At Risk, 1985 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-340)
    - America At Risk, 1985 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-341)
    - America At Risk, 1985 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-342)
    - America At Risk, 1985 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-343)
    - America At Risk, 1985 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-361)
    - America At Risk, 1985 (Box 61, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-130)
    - America At Risk, 1985 Sept. 26 (Box 39, Film-reel RL11802-F16-139)
    - America At Risk, 1985 Sept. 26 (Box 55, Film-reel RL11802-F16-153)
    - America At Risk Part 1, 1985 (Box 17, Film-reel RL11802-F16-080)
    - America At Risk Part 2, Undated (Box 29, Film-reel RL11802-F16-125)
    - America At Risk: A History of Consumer Protest, 1985 (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0157)
    - America At Risk: A History of Consumer Protest, 1985 (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0158)
    - America At Risk: A History of Consumer Protest, 1985 Mar. 14 (Box 28, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-005)
    - America At Risk: A History of Consumer Protest, 1985 Sept. 08 (Box 42, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-091)
    - Blowpipes and Bulldozers, Undated (Box 120, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0479)
    - Boost the Value of Your Home, 2002 Oct. 26 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1235)
    - Broadcast Journalism #296d, Undated (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-102)
    - Burglar Proofing Your Home & Car, 1987 (Box 83, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0448)
    - Burglar Proofing Your Home & Car, 1987 (Box 83, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0461)
    - Buy Me That! #1, Undated (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-052)
    - Buy Me That! #2, Undated (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-051)
    - Buy Me That! #3, Undated (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-050)
    - Buyer's Market from Consumer Reports, 1998 Nov. 02 (Box 99, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-226)
    - Buying Clothes, 2003 June (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1233)
    - Buying Your Own Policy, 2002 Aug. 06 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0715)
    - By the Numbers, 1993 Dec. 13 (Box 37, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-062)
    - Caveat Venditor Show #4, Undated (Box 76, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-083)
    - Cell Phones, 2005 Feb. 03 (Box 99, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0929)
    - Cell Phones, Interview with Alberto Rojas, 2004 Feb. 04 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1181)
    - Check It Out, 1993 Sept. 23 (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0159)
    - Children & TV ADS, 1991 (Box 120, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-220)
    - Children's Damaged Fingers, 2004 Apr. 07 (Box 85, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-371)
    - Choicepoint ID Theft Gail Hillebrand Interviews, Undated (Box 105, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0388)
    - Conference Council on Consumer Information Session on Consumer Financial Problems, 1962 Mar. 30 (Box 74, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-033)
    - Conference Council on Consumer Information Session on Consumer Financial Problems, 1962 Mar. 30 (Box 74, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-034)
    - Conn Con Report #4, Undated (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-272)
    - Conn Con Report #5, Undated (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-273)
    - Conn Con Report 3, Undated (Box 120, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-122)
    - Consumer Reports Tape 2, Undated (Box 99, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-227)
    - Consumer Symposium table 1b, Undated (Box 73, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-074)
    - Consumer Symposium Tape #1a, Undated (Box 73, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-073)
    - Consumer Symposium tape #2, Undated (Box 73, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-075)
    - Consumer Symposium Tape #3, Undated (Box 73, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-078)
    - Consumer Symposium Tape #7, Undated (Box 73, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-076)
    - Consumer Symposium Tape #8, Undated (Box 73, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-077)
    - Consumer Union Tape 2, 1969 Aug. 16 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-114)
    - Consumer Union Tape 2, 1969 Aug. 16 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-115)
    - Consumer Want to Know, 1960 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-354)
    - Consumer Want to Know, 1960 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-355)
    - Consumerism: Let the Seller Beware, Undated (Box 17, Film-reel RL11802-F16-078)
    - Consumerism: Let the Seller Beware, Undated (Box 34, Film-reel RL11802-F16-135)
    - Consumerism: Let the Seller Beware, Undated (Box 34, Film-reel RL11802-F16-138)
    - Consumerism: Let the Seller Beware #3, Undated (Box 59, Film-reel RL11802-F16-170)
    - Consumers Challenge Bdcst. #192, 1974 Mar. 03 (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-125)
    - Consumers Want to Know, 1960 (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-056)
    - Consumers Want to Know, 1960 (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-057)
    - Consumers Want to Know, 1961 (Box 3, Film-reel RL11802-F16-042)
    - Consumers Want to Know, 1961 (Box 3, Film-reel RL11802-F16-045)
    - Consumers Want to Know, 1961 (Box 39, Film-reel RL11802-F16-140)
    - Consumers Want to Know, 1961 (Box 48, Film-reel RL11802-F16-156)
    - Consumers Want to Know 1960, 1996 Mar. 19 (Box 1, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-013)
    - Consumers Want to Know 1960, 1996 Mar. 19 (Box 60, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-107)
    - Copy- Discussion on Trading Stamps by Farm Bureau Mendon River-Side Advisory Council in Mercer County, 1973 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-146)
    - Cordless Phones; High-tech toys; Fitness Equipment; Garbage Bags; Laundry Detergents, 2002 Nov.; 1999 Nov.; 2003 Nov.; 2000 May (Box 99, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0921)
    - CR Flatware, New Tax Law, Mac/Page Maker 4.0, 1991 Mar. (Box 137, Disk RL11802-FD-005)
    - CR Flatware, New Tax Law, Mac/Page Maker 4.0, 1991 Mar. (Box 137, Disk RL11802-FD-006)
    - CR Selling It Once Over Mac/Page Maker 4.0, 1991 Mar. (Box 137, Disk RL11802-FD-004)
    - CR Selling It Once Over Mac/Page Maker 4.0, 1991 Mar. (Box 137, Disk RL11802-FD-007)
    - Credit Buying, 1961 Sept. 06 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-144)
    - Cyrus Richardson Larkin H.S., Elgin, IL #141, 1974 June 12 (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-064)
    - David Heim on Best Buy Electronic Gifts, 2003 Nov. 15 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0713)
    - David Herm on Best Buy Gifts, 2003 Dec. 05 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0716)
    - De Mananitas. Insurance Tips from CR. 50 ways to save, 2002 May 08 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1226)
    - Dean Gallea, Bus Week TV, Computer Upgrade, 2002 Jan. 27 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1177)
    - Debit Cards with Mari McQueen, 2001 Sept. 08 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0660)
    - Deconstruction Home Security DCON-208, Undated (Box 1, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-003)
    - Dialogo Con Glenis Topico: Reporta al Consumidor, 2001 Nov. 14 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0654)
    - Dialogue 101, 1992 Nov. 22 (Box 85, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-208)
    - Discussion by Mendon Riverside Advisory Council Trading Stamps, 1962 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-112)
    - Dollar Decisions Telecourse, Undated (Box 62, Film-reel RL11802-F16-173)
    - Dollar Decisions Telecourse CEW, Undated (Box 62, Film-reel RL11802-F16-174)
    - Dollar Stores, 2005 Mar. 18 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0870)
    - Drugstore Survey, 1999 Sept. 28 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0963)
    - Ear Defenders, Undated (Box 70, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-152)
    - Education, Undated (Box 76, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-090)
    - Education/Zillions, 1993 Feb. 25 (Box 58, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0017)
    - Elaine Cantor Utica Free Acad., NY #142, 1974 June 13 (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-065)
    - Electronics for the Holidays, Holiday Special, 2004 Dec. 19 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0792)
    - Electronics picks/Gotchas, 2004 Oct. 23 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0841)
    - Empowering Tomorrow's Consumer, 2011 May 03-06 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-347)
    - Entertainment Programming #296e, Undated (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-103)
    - Escape from Suburbia, Undated (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-048)
    - Evenflo Infant Carries Recall, 2001 May 01 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0998)
    - Exploring the Marketplace: The Claims and the Facts #249 (3 copies), Undated (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-154)
    - Exploring the Marketplace: The Claims and the Facts #249 (3 copies), Undated (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-155)
    - Exploring the Marketplace: The Claims and the Facts #249 (3 copies), Undated (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-156)
    - Extra help the How-to Channel, 1998 Jan. 20 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0613)
    - Fast Talk, 1985 Sept. 30 (Box 38, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-013)
    - Fix it or Nix it, 2005 Sept. 27 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0821)
    - Frauds, Undated (Box 76, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-108)
    - Garbage Garbage -- Two full versions #248, Undated (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-153)
    - Gene Kimmelman Telecommunications, 2001 Feb. 16 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0714)
    - Gerard SanGemino, Nanuet H.S., Nanuet, NY #140, 1974 June 12 (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-063)
    - Get it Right, 2001 Feb. 20 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-244)
    - Getting Your Money's Worth Milk, Toys, Shoes #183, 1940 (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-073)
    - Great Rate - Tod Marks Food for Thought, Undated (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1216)
    - Help with a Few Things?, 2003 July 10 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1200)
    - Home Safe Home, 1986 (Box 85, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0369)
    - Home Safe Home, 1986 (Box 85, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0370)
    - Home Safe Home, 1986 (Box 83, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0447)
    - Home Safe Home, 1986 (Box 83, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0457)
    - Houses and Condos, 1986 (Box 83, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0458)
    - How to Cut Cooling Costs, 2004 June 17 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0760)
    - How to get a Better Price, 2005 Apr. 07 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0807)
    - How to Spend Less Traveling and Enjoying it More, 1986 (Box 85, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0371)
    - How to Spend Less Traveling and Enjoying it More, 1986 (Box 83, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0445)
    - How to Spend Less Traveling and Enjoying it More, 1986 (Box 83, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0460)
    - Inflatable Pool Safety, 2005 May (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1149)
    - Inflatable Pools f/ Don Mays, Sr. Director, Product Safety & Consumer Science, 2005 May (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1145)
    - Introduction, Undated (Box 76, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-093)
    - Is Someone There, Undated (Box 20, Film-reel RL11802-F16-110)
    - J Guin Ch. 5? re: airplane air, Undated (Box 68, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0088)
    - Jeff Fox on Spam, 2003 July 13 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1231)
    - Jim Guest Cell Phones, 2003 Jan. 08 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0736)
    - Jim Guest Do Not Call, 200 Oct. 01 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1228)
    - Jim Guest: Spam, 2004 Aug. 10 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0829)
    - Junk Mail, 1973 July 18 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-139)
    - Junk Mail, 1973 July 27 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-131)
    - Kids and Commercials, Undated (Box 26, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-035)
    - Kim Kleman CR.org Bike Helmet Safety, 2005 May 20 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1140)
    - Kim Kleman Discussing Upromise, 2001 Nov. 23 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0973)
    - Len Sirotzky Schaumberg Elem. Sch. #139, 1974 June 12 (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-062)
    - Lifetime Live Laundry Detergents, 2000 Oct. 02 (Box 106, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1004)
    - Mandy Walker: Best Time to Buy Particular Products, 2004 May 20 (Box 106, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1021)
    - Manufactured Landscapes, 2006 (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-036)
    - Mari McQueen Making Your House Pay Off, 2002 Oct. 09 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1227)
    - Mari McQueen on ID Theft, 2005 June 20 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0867)
    - Marketplace, 1981 Dec. 06 (Box 16, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-008)
    - Maxed Out, Undated (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-041)
    - Michigan Credit Union League, Credit Union National Association (CUNA International)--How to Handle $300,000 A Little at a Time, approximately 1972 (Box 125, Audio-phonodisc RL11802-PD-035)
    - Michigan Credit Union League, Credit Union National Association (CUNA International)--How to Handle $300,000 A Little at a Time new version, approximately 1972 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F35-021)
    - Michigan Credit Union League, Credit Union National Association (CUNA International)--How to Handle $300,000 A Little at a Time old version, approximately 1972 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F35-022)
    - Money to Burn, 1984 Aug. 10 (Box 41, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-019)
    - Money to Burn, 1985 Sept. 30 (Box 38, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-014)
    - Money to Burn, 1985 Sept. 30 (Box 36, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-017)
    - Mori McQueen: Recalls Pt. 2, 2004 Oct. 14 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1123)
    - Mow, ???? Dec. 03 (Box 120, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-215)
    - National Consumer Finance Association, Family Finances series FS16, 1968 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F35-013)
      Scope and Contents
      791. Our Living American Economy: Money Has Meaning
    - National Consumer Finance Association, Family Finances series FS16, 1968 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F35-014)
      792. Our Living American Economy: Money Makes Cents